lowdownlist.net 2013-09-15

# Privacy Policy

**Lowdownlist.net Privacy Policy**

At Lowdownlist.net we appreciate your privacy and hope that you feel comfortable trusting us. Lowdownlist.net provides a comparison shopping service that enables consumers to compare prices, products and stores when they shop online. We believe that you have a right to know what information we collect, how we intend to use that information, whom we intend to share it with, and what measures we take to keep that information secure. 

This privacy statement describes how Low Down Media LLC collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Web site: www.lowdownlist.net. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

Low Down Media LLC has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The TRUSTe program covers information collected through this Web site, www.lowdownlist.net. TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us [privacy@lowdownlist.net](mailto:privacy@lowdownlist.net) or 3313 West Cherry Lane, Suite 336, Meridian, ID 83642.  If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint).

**Collecting Your Information**

We collect information at several stages during your interaction with our site. When you first enter our site, we note your IP address and time of your visit. As you browse the site, we record your zipcode via a cookie so we can serve more location specific information on your next visit. We will not collect any personally identifiable information about you. Cookies do not recognise you as a person, just your computer.

You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits although in that case you may not be able to use certain features on our site.

When you use our contact us option we collect your name and email address. We use this to respond to your questions and concerns.

**Third Party Advertising**

We work with third parties who use cookies to collect non-personally identifiable information when you visit our Web site and other sites. This information may be used to provide you with better shopping or savings opportunities through advertisements on this and other Web sites that you visit, or to conduct market research and website analysis. The use of cookies by our third party advertising providers is not covered by our privacy policy.  We do not have access or control over these cookies.

**Widgets**

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button [and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site]. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it

**Sharing of information**

Lowdownlist.net does not share any contact information or IP address information with its partners. We will only use information that helps our customers to find the lowest prices. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

We may also disclose your personal information

  * as required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,
  * if Low Down Media LLC is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information, 
  * to any other third party with your prior consent to do so. 

Any user statistics that we may provide to prospective advertisers or partners regarding your Lowdownlist.net usage are provided in the aggregate only and do not include any personally identifiable information about any individual user. 

**How We Protect Your Information**

The privacy and protection of your personal information is vitally important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us <http://lowdownlist.net/contact.aspx>

**Your Submitted Personally Identifiable Information**

Please note that users can not update or delete previously submitted information. If your information (such as your email address) should change, we ask that you re-submit your request.

**Data Retention**

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at privacy@lowdownlist.net.  We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

**Links to Other Web Sites** ****

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Low Down Media LLC. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit. 

**Notification of Privacy Policy Changes**

This Website Privacy Statement is effective as of the date listed below. Even if you read and/or agreed to a prior policy statement, you need to review this updated version. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, or other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. If, however, we are going to use users personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users by posting a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective.

**Questions?**

We welcome any questions or comments you have about our privacy practices. Please feel free to contact us at: [Feedback](http://www.lowdownlist.net/contact.aspx).

3313 West Cherry Lane, Suite 336, Meridian ID,  83642

**Effective Date: Privacy Notice last modified July 16, 2013.**
